Instructor: When we have items in our shopping cart
and when a user clicks on the summary page,
what is it that we want?
We want to display a page where
on the right side we will see all the products.
And on the left side we will capture the information
for shipping details.
Like we will need name, phone numbers, street address,
and once we get all the address details
then we will have a pattern to place order.
So rather than designing that page,
I have provided that design in the (indistinct).
If you go to section 10, that will be a summary U I.
Copy everything there
and we need to create an action method for that.
And then create a view.
In the card controller here right after index,
let me create an action method
which will have I action result.
Call that as summary.
And for now, let me just return
back to the view, right click here, add a view.
We will give it the exact same name, which is summary.
Let's add that.
And I will paste all the H T M L that we copied
from the template.
Now again, you can see here it is all H T M L
and C S S and nothing related to dot net core.
So there are no tag helpers or any eraser code
purely H T M L, and C S S .
And we will go to index here
where we have the summary link here.
We will go to E S P Action of summary.
Let me run the project
and take a look at the UI that we pasted.
Let me go to shopping cart and here, rather than
displaying zero, let me open underscore layout for now
and I will remove that because we do not have zero items.
We actually have items in the cart.
That looks good.
If we navigate the shopping cart,
and if I go to summary here, great.
You can see we have to provide the shipping details here
all of the fields
and we have to populate the order summary as well.
When a user populates this information,
where will we hold that information?
When an order is actually placed in a typical website,
we have all of this information
in order header and then in order details.
We have all the product details inside that order
but we do not have a model for that.
So let me create that model first
for order header and order details in the next video.